Finding Aid for the Phyllis Diller papers, 1934-2011 LSC.1893
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Jokes and Gags, 1964-1988
  - Jokes and Gags, 1964-1988 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    Representative examples of Phyllis Diller's binders (used to house the jokes and gags in this series), saved for informational purposes.
- Photographs, Circa 1950-Circa 2010
  Includes photographs (mostly 8x10) of Diller with various celebrities, portraits of Diller, snapshots from the opening of the Lima Civic Center in Lima, OH, and a photograph of Oscar (Dub) Johnson, a pianist who worked with Diller at The Purple Onion nightclub in San Francisco, CA. The series is pre-dominantly composed of portraits.
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 25, Folder 3)
    Photographs of Phyllis Diller with celebrities in various decades, including Barbra Streisand, Bob Hope, James Stewart, and Johnny Carson.
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 25, Folder 4)
    Portraits of Diller in various decades.
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
    Photographs from the opening of Lima Civic Center in Lima, OH; photograph of Oscar (Dub) Johnson, pianist who worked with Diller at The Purple Onion in San Francisco, CA; color print outs of photographs of the interiors of Diller's house.
- Sheet Music, 1934-Circa 1980
  Includes sheet music from various periods in Diller's career.
  - "Phyllis Diller's Old Music from Sherwood Music School Days and Alameda", Circa 1934-1956
    Contains sheet music from Diller's three years at Sherwood Music Conservatory in Chicago, IL (1934-1938?) and Alameda, CA (1945-approx. 1956). In Alameda, Diller began writing, performing, and eventually touring with her comedy. Subseries includes mostly published classical music and standards. Of particular interest are workbooks from some of Diller's courses at Sherwood Music School.
    - Sheet Music, Circa 1934-1956 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      Includes music from Sherwood Music Conservatory and Alameda, CA.
    - Sheet Music, Circa 1934-1956 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Sheet Music, Circa 1934-1956 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Sheet Music, Circa 1934-1956 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Sheet Music, Circa 1934-1956 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Sheet Music, Circa 1934-1956 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Sheet Music, Circa 1934-1956 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Sheer Music, Circa 1934-1956 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Sheet Music, Circa 1934-1938 (Box 27, Folder 4)
      Sheet music and lesson books from Sherwood Music Conservatory, some with notes by Diller.
    - Sheet Music, Circa 1934-1938 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Sheet Music, Circa 1934-1956 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Sheet Music, Circa 1934-1956 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Sheet Music, Circa 1934-1956 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Sheet Music, 1934-1956 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Sheet Music, 1934-1956 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Sheet Music, 1934-1956 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Sheet Music, 1934-1956 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - "Born to Sing" album music, Circa 1970
    Music from Diller's album "Born to Sing," released by Columbia in 1970. Includes songs that were not included on the final album.
    - Sheet Music, Circa 1970 (Box 29, Folder 1)
      Music from Diller's album "Born to Sing," released by Columbia in 1970.
  - "Best of Broadway", Undated
    Sheet music labelled "Best of Broadway." It is likely that this sheet music is from "The Phyllis Diller Show," a 90-minute special that aired on NBC in the 1960s (exact date unknown). This special, which is different from (and likely preceded) the sitcom "The Phyllis Diller Show," was presented by "The Best of Broadway." See also press kit in: Box 65, Folder 1.
    - Sheet Music, Undated (Box 29, Folder 2)
      Sheet music labeled "Best of Broadway."
    - Sheet Music, Undated (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Sheet Music, Undated (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Sheet Music, Undated (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Sheet Music, Undated (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Sheet Music, Undated (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Sheet Music, Undated (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Music from "The Hollywood Palace" TV series, Circa 1964-1970
    This show was broadcast on the ABC network, 1964-1970. Songs include: "Diller Opening," "Love Story," and "Wives and Lovers."
    - Sheet Music, Circa 1964-1970 (Box 31, Folder 1)
      Songs include: "Diller Opening," "Love Story," and "Wives and Lovers."
  - L.P. Files, Undated
    Materials from files marked "L.P. File" and "Record." It is unclear which of Diller's released albums (if any) are related to these materials. It is most likely that they relate to her album "Born to Sing" (released by Columbia in 1970), as this is Diller's only released album that contains songs. Folders include sheet music, written and typed lyrics (for songs including "Dancing in the Street," "With a Little Help from My Friends," and "Ticket to Ride,") memos and notes, song lists, lighting and sound requirements for a live performance, and occasional drawings on the margins of papers (presumably by Diller). Some materials are printed on the back of stationary from the radio station KROW, where Diller began her career as a copywriter in 1952. The stationery includes copy from this period, possibly written by Diller. These folders were originally housed with Diller's sheet music.
    - Sheet Music, Undated (Box 31, Folder 2)
      Materials from file marked "L.P. File." Folders include sheet music, written and typed lyrics (for songs including "Dancing in the Street," "With a Little Help from My Friends," and "Ticket to Ride,") memos and notes, song lists, and lighting and sound requirements for a live performance. Some materials are printed on the back of stationery from the radio station KROW, where Diller began her career as a copywriter in 1952. The stationery includes copy from this period, possibly written by Diller.
    - Sheet Music, Undated (Box 31, Folder 3)
      Materials from file marked "Record." Folders include sheet music, written and typed lyrics (for songs including "When I Fall In Love," "I've Got the World on a String," and "The Nearness of You"), memos and notes, and drawings in margins of papers (presumably by Diller).
    - Sheet Music, Undated (Box 31, Folder 4)
      Materials from an unmarked file that houses similar materials to folders 3 and 4.
  - "The Pat Boone Show" TV series., December 1966
    Sheet music for Diller and Boone's duet of "I Remember It Well."
    - Sheet Music, December 1966-1968. (Box 31, Folder 5)
      Sheet music from Diller and Boone's duet of "I Remember It Well," which appeared on the NBC series "The Pat Boone Show" in 1966-1968 (likely December 21 or 22, 1966).
  - "The Beautiful Phyllis Diller Show" TV series., October 1968
    Sheet music for "The Beautiful Phyllis Diller Show," Diller's variety series which ran for one season on NBC in 1968. Folders are organized by episode. When possible, numbers from episodes have been placed together in chronological order within the series. However, sometimes episodes are placed out of chronological order and/or broken up, maintaining the organizational structure of the original collection and allowing sheet music of different sizes to be housed in appropriate boxes. Scope and content notes inform the reader when the music from an episode is broken up within the series, and in which boxes and folders the remaining music from that episode can be found. All songs contained in each folder are listed in scope and content notes.
    - Sheet Music, Undated (Box 30, Folder 2)
      Sheet music for unknown episode, including "2 Bar Playoff," "Transition-I," "Transition II," "Theme Pretty," and "Funny Playoff 2."
    - Sheet Music, Undated (Box 30, Folder 3)
      Sheet music for unknown episode, including "Funny Playoff 2," "Theme in 4 Long," "Theme in 3 Long," "Blackout Theme 1," "Blackout Theme-2," "Funny Play On," "Old Fanfare & "Play Off," and "Fanfare."
    - Sheet Music, Undated (Box 30, Folder 4)
      Sheet music for unknown episode, including "Phyllis' Phollies," "Short Comedy Bridge," "Hooray for Hollyballoon," and "Chicken-Playoff."
    - Sheet Music, October 20, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 6)
      Sheet music for "We've Got To Be Young," which Diller sang with Glen Campbell and Kate Smith in Season 1, Episode 6. (1 of 8, see Box 37, Folders 3-5)
    - Sheet Music, September 15, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 5)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode One, including "Don't Give Up," "James Knox Polka," and "Carson Play Off." (1 of 5, see Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Sheet Music, September 15, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 6)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode One, including "Sing, Sing, Sing."
    - Sheet Music, September 15, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 1)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode One, including "Opening-Version-2," "Opening Billboard," "Wine and Roses-Intro," "Wine and Roses," "Wine and Roses Play-off." (2 of 5, see Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Sheet Music, September 22, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 2)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Two including "A Train," "James Knox Polka," and "Carson Play Off." (1 of 6)
    - Sheet Music, September 22, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 3)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Two, including "The Look of Love," "Hooray Gompers," "Gomper's Stomp," and "Look of Love." (2 of 6)
    - Sheet Music, September 22, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 4)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Two, including "The Look of Love." (3 of 6, see Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Sheet Music, September 29, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 5)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Three, including "Strictly for the Birds" and "Everyday Housewife." (1 of 9)
    - Sheet Music, September 29, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 6)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Three, including "The Bird" and "Doodle Town Lead In." (2 of 9)
    - Sheet Music, September 29, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 1)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Three, including "Ev'ryday Housewife" and "Doodle Town Lead-In." (3 of 9, see Box 44, Folders 8-10)
    - Sheet Music, October 6, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 2)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Four, including "We Jog" and "The Men in My Little Girl's Life." (1 of 10)
    - Sheet Music, October 6, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 3)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Four, including "Jogging Jokes," "We Jog Reprise," and "Susan B. Anthony." (2 of 10)
    - Sheet Music, October 6, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 4)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Four, including "Nobody Wants to Pet." (3 of 10, see Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Sheet Music, October 13, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 5)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Five, including "Spanish Phyl Reprise," "Spanish, Anyone," and "Fountain of Youth." (1 of 9)
    - Sheet Music, October 13, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 6)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Five, including "Yellow Days," "Fountain of Youth," and Ponce de Leon." (2 of 9)
    - Sheet Music, October 13, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 1)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Five, including "We've Got To Be Young," "Yellow Days," "Spanish Anyone," and "Fountain of Youth." (3 of 9)
    - Sheet Music, October 13, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 2)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Five, including "More," "Ponce de Leon," and "We've Got To Be Young." (4 of 9, see Box 34, Folders 3-7)
    - Sheet Music, October 20, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 3)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Six, including "Stepping Out." (2 of 8)
    - Sheet Music, October 20, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 4)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Six, including "Gardner" and "Buzz Off." (3 of 8)
    - Sheet Music, October 20, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 5)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Six, including "The Man I Love," "Gardener," and "Stepping Out." (4 of 8, see Box 45, Folders 3-5)
    - Sheet Music, Circa November 3, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 6)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Seven, including "Y B B Waltz Chorus," "Y B B Playoff I," "Y B B Playoff II." (1 of 7)
    - Sheet Music, Circa October 1968. (Box 38, Folder 1)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Seven, including "Shoot'em Up." (2 of 7)
    - Sheet Music, Circa October 1968. (Box 38, Folder 2)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Seven, including "This Guy's In Love With You," "Phyllis' Fugue," "Flushed from the Bathroom of Your Heart," "Buffalo Shuffle," "Shoot'em Up," "The Saints," and "Come Back to Me," (3 of 7, see Box 43, Folders 9-12)
    - Sheet Music, November 3, 1968 (Box 38, Folder 3)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Eight, including "Honey," "Pooh Pooh P.T. Barnum," "Shangri-La Play Off," "Circus Transition," "Dionne [Warwick] Medley," and "Honey." (1 of 11)
    - Sheet Music, November 3, 1968 (Box 38, Folder 4)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Eight, including "I Lost My Kidney in Sidney," "How Did You Do It?" and "Midway." (2 of 11)
    - Sheet Music, November 3, 1968 (Box 38, Folder 5)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Eight, including "Midway Part 2," ""Always Something," "Dionne [Warwick] Medley," "Ballgame Play Off," and "A Day for the Unholidayed." (3 of 11, see Box 42, Folders 8-9)
    - Sheet Music, November 3, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 1)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Eight, including "Ball Game-Playon," Ball Game-Playoff."
    - Sheet Music, November 10, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 2)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Nine, (the sheet music is dated October 1, 1968), including "Home-Military," "Learn to Fly," and "If I Had a Hammer." (1 of 11)
    - Sheet Music, November 10 1968 (Box 39, Folder 3)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Nine, (the sheet music is dated October 1, 1968), including "Carrie Nation Rag." (2 of 11)
    - Sheet Music, November 10, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 4)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Nine, (the sheet music is dated October 1, 1968), including "Carrie Button," "Dirty Movies," and "If I Had a Hammer." (3 of 11)
    - Sheet Music, November 10, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 5)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Nine, (the sheet music is dated October 1, 1968), including "I Will Wait For You," "Home-Military," "Sock'em Carrie," and "Learn to Fly." (4 of 11, see Box 45, Folders 10-12)
    - Sheet Music, November 17, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 6)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Ten, including "One More Dance," "Gee Mr. Webster," "Communication Gap," "One More Dance," "Singing in Rain," "The Communication Gap," "One More Dance," and "Country Boy." (1 of 10)
    - Sheet Music, November 17, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 1)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Ten, including "Finian's Medley." (2 of 10)
    - Sheet Music, November 17, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 2)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Ten, including "Communication Gap." (3 of 10, see Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Sheet Music, November 24, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 3)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode 11, including "Sam Morse-Of Course," Soldier, Soldier," "Caper," and "The Morse Code." (1 of 7)
    - Sheer Music, November 24, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 4)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode 11, including "The Morse Code," "On Wings of Song-Ending," "Caper," "Rustle of Spring-Ending," and "The Morse Code." (2 of 7)
    - Sheet Music, November 24, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 5)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode 11, including "Soldier." (3 of 7, see Box 44, Folders 1-4)
    - Sheet Music, November 1968 (Box 41, Folder 1)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode 12. Songs including "Lulu,-All I Need" and "Your Gourmet Dish." (1 of 11)
    - Sheet Music, November 1968 (Box 41, Folder 2)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode 12. Songs including "Lulu All I Need." (2 of 11)
    - Sheet Music, November 1968 (Box 41, Folder 3)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode 12. Songs including "And So We Sew." (3 of 11)
    - Sheet Music, November 1968 (Box 41, Folder 4)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode 12. Songs including "And So We Sew." (4 of 11)
    - Sheet Music, November 1968 (Box 41, Folder 5)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode 12. Songs including "Love Potent," "My Son," and "The Peeler." (5 of 11, see Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Sheet Music, September 22, 1968 (Box 41, Folder 6)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Two. Songs including "Hallelujah Ending." (4 of 6, see Box 44, Folders 6 and 7)
    - Sheet Music, November 17, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 1)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Ten. Songs including "One More Dance." (4 of 10, see Box 46, Folders 7-11)
    - Sheet Music, Circa November 1968 (Box 42, Folder 2)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode 12. Songs including "Your Gourmet Dish." (6 of 11)
    - Sheet Music, Circa November 1968 (Box 42, Folder 3)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode 12. Songs including "The Peeler," and "Love Potent." (7 of 11)
    - Sheet Music, Circa November 1968 (Box 42, Folder 4)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode 12. Songs including "Lulu-All I Need." (8 of 11)
    - Sheet Music, Circa November 1968 (Box 42, Folder 5)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode 12. Songs including "Lulu-All I Need" and "My Son." (9 of 11)
    - Sheet Music, Circa November 1968 (Box 42, Folder 6)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode 12. Songs including "My Son." (10 of 11)
    - Sheet Music, Circa November 1968 (Box 42, Folder 7)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode 12. Songs including "And So We Sew." (11 of 11)
    - Sheet Music, November 3, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 8)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Eight. Songs including "How Did You Do It," "Ball Game Playon," and "Ball Game Playoff." (4 of 11)
    - Sheet Music, November 1968 (Box 42, Folder 9)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Eight. Songs including "Honey." (5 of 11, see Box 45, Folders 6-9)
    - Sheet Music, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 10)
      Numbers in this folder are labeled 1-7. However, it is unclear in which episode the numbers were used. Songs including "Theme in 3 Long."
    - Sheet Music, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 11)
      Numbers in this folder are labeled 8-16. However, it is unclear in which episode the numbers were used. Songs including "A Day for the Unholidayed", Funny Playoff #2", and "Wine and Roses Intro".
    - Sheet Music, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 12)
      Numbers in this folder are labeled 16A-18. However, it is unclear in which episode the numbers were used. Songs including "Wine and Roses," "Theme Pretty," and "Hooray for Hollyballoon."
    - Sheet Music, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 1)
      Numbers in this folder are labeled 19-40. However, it is unclear in which episode the numbers were used. Songs including "Blackout Theme #1" and "Closing Theme."
    - Sheet Music, September 15, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 2)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode One. Songs including "Opening Billboard," "Carson Play-off," "Phyllis Phollies." (3 of 5, see Box 46, Folders 1 & 2)
    - Sheet Music, October 13, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 3)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Five. Songs including "Yellow Days" and "Ponce de Leon." (5 of 9)
    - Sheet Music, October 13, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 4)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Five. Songs including "More" and "Ponce de Leon." (6 of 9)
    - Sheet Music, October 13, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 5)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Five. Songs including "We've Got To Be Young." (7 of 9)
    - Sheet Music, October 13, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 6)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Five. Songs including "Spanish, Anyone." (8 of 9)
    - Sheet Music, October 13, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 7)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Five. Songs including "Spanish, Anyone" and "Spanish Phyl-Reprise" (9 of 9)
    - Sheet Music, October 6, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 8)
      Sheet music for titled "Jogging Jokes." It is unspecified in which episode this number was performed. However, it was likely in episode four, in which the number "We Jog" was featured. (4 of 10, see Box 47, Folders 3-8)
    - Sheet Music, October 1968 (Box 43, Folder 9)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Seven. Songs including "Back to Bach." (4 of 7)
    - Sheet Music, November, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 10)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Seven. Songs including "Shoot'em Up." (5 of 7)
    - Sheet Music, November, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 11)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Seven. Songs including "Shoot'em Up." (6 of 7)
    - Sheet Music, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 12)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Seven. Songs including "The Saint" and "Y B B Waltz." (7 of 7)
    - Sheet Music, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 13)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Seven. Songs including "Flushed From the Bathroom of Your Heart." (4 of 5)
    - Sheet Music, November, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 14)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Seven. The episode aired in November, 1968 on NBC. Songs including "Come Back To Me," "Buffalo Shuffle," "Phyllis' Fugue," "This Guy's," and "Shoot'em Up." (4 of 5)
    - Sheet Music, November 24, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 1)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode 11. Songs including "Sam Morse-Of course." (4 of 7)
    - Sheet Music, November 24, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 2)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode 11. Songs including "Sam Morse-Of course." (5 of 7)
    - Sheet Music, November 24, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 3)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode 11. Songs including "Soldier, Soldier." (6 of 7)
    - Sheet Music, November 24, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 4)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode 11. Songs including "Caper." (7 of 7)
    - Sheet Music, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 5)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode 14. Songs including "On Wings of Song."
    - Sheet Music, September 22, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 6)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Two. Songs including "Gompers Stomp." (5 of 6)
    - Sheet Music, September 22, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 7)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Two. Songs including "Gompers Stomp" and "Hooray Gompers." (6 of 6)
    - Sheet Music, September 29, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 8)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Three. Songs including "Doodle Town Lead In." (4 of 9)
    - Sheet Music, September 29, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 9)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Three. Songs including "Everyday Housewife." (5 of 9)
    - Sheet Music, September 29, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 10)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Three. Songs including "Everyday Housewife." (6 of 9)
    - Sheet Music, September 29, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 1)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Three. Songs including "Strictly for the Birds." (7 of 9)
    - Sheet Music, September 29, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 2)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Three. Songs including "The Bird" (8 of 9, see Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Sheet Music, October 20, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 3)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Six. Songs including "Fountain of Youth" and "Stepping Out." (5 of 8)
    - Sheet Music, October 20, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 4)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Six. Songs include "Stepping Out" and "Buzz Off." (6 of 8, see Box 47, Folders 9-10)
    - Sheet Music, November 3, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 5)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Eight. Songs including "Midway" (6 of 11)
    - Sheet Music, November 3, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 6)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Eight. Songs including "Midway." (7 of 11)
    - Sheet Music, November 3, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 7)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Eight. Songs including "Midway-Part II." (8 of 11)
    - Sheet Music, November 3, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 8)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Eight. Songs including "Shangri-La Play-On" and "Midway-Part II." (9 of 11, see Box 47, Folders 11-12)
    - Sheet Music, November 10, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 9)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Nine. Songs including "Sock'em Carrie," "Home Military" and "I Will Wait For You." (5 out of 11)
    - Sheet Music, November 10, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 10)
      Sheet music for Season One, Episode Nine. Songs including "I Will Wait For You." (6 out of 11)